pintastic.com 2017-02-28

# Pintastic Pricacy Policy - Pinterest ™ Clone Script - Pintastic Ultimate Pinboard

Pintastic values the privacy and security of the information that you share with us through www.Pintastic.com (the “Web Site”). It is important that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices, the choices you may make about how we collect and use your information at this Web Site, and the ways you may contact us.

We may change this Privacy Polic from time to time.  Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective upon posting.  Please check back periodically for updates.  If at any point we decide to use Personal Information in a manner that is materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this new manner.

The amount, type, and use of information we collect depends on how you use this Web Site.  This Privacy Policy applies only to the practices of Pintastic and its employees.  Pintastic will not apply the provisions of this Privacy Policy to Business Contact Information or Aggregated Information.

**Definitions**  
“Personal Information” includes, your name, address information, personal e-mail address and URL, account username and password, as well as other, similar information. “Non-Identifying Personal Information” includes information about you, including, without limitation, your Internet service provider, browser type, domain name, the Web Site that referred you to us, the web pages you request, the date and time of those requests, and entry and exit points.

**Collection of Personal Information or Prospect Information**  
Pintastic may collect Personal Information from you, but only if you provide it to us voluntarily. We also collect Personal Information that you provide to our suppliers, which they pass on to us so that we can fulfill your order.  You must provide Personal Information in the form of a unique identifier (username, password) to enter certain parts of our web site.  In addition, in certain situations, such as when a purchaser buys a product as a gift and supplies the recipients’ name and address, we collect Prospect Information.

**Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Personal Information**  
During your use of our Web Site, we will collect certain Non-Identifying Personal Information to enhance the functionality of the Web Site and to make your access more convenient and efficient.  We retain Non-Identifying Personal Information and use it to establish Web Site activity trends, monitor Web Site performance, improve Web Site design and functionality, fulfill orders, inform current and potential customers and suppliers about our services, and for other business purposes.  Our collection of Non-Identifying Personal Information may involve the use of cookies.  Among other uses, cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests, to save you from re-entering your registration data at each connection, and to provide features such as online customer payment and shopping carts. No personal or unencrypted information will be encoded in cookies that are stored on your computer.

**Use of Personal Information**  
Pintastic may use and disclose Personal Information or Prospect Information as described in this document.  In addition to the uses described in this document, we may use Personal Information or Prospect Information for purposes that include maintaining the Web Site, order fulfillment and administration, and product surveys, administrative and analytical purposes like accounting, billing and audits, and information system management, and other, similar uses.  We may also use Personal Information or Prospect Information to provide current and potential customers and suppliers with information about our services.

We only collect, use, and disclose Personal Information or Prospect Information for purposes that are reasonable in the circumstances.  We use only fair and lawful means to collect Personal Information or Prospect Information.

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you.  Only Pintastic (or agents working on behalf of Pintastic and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings.  If you do not want receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information.  Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of Pintastic's marketing list or update your information by notifying us at support@pintastic.com.
